New York State Department of Labor Files 6152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Hearings Conducted for the Purpose of Establishing the Value of Gratuities Received by Service Employees in the Restaurant and Hotel-Restaurant Industry 25 - 0068, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Hearings Conducted for the Purpose of Establishing the Value of Gratuities Received by Employees in the Barber Shop Industry 25 - 0069, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Garages, Gas Stations + Parking Lot Attendants April 17, 1947. 25 - 0070 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Hearings before the Industrial Commissioner State of New York on Schedule 1 - Value of Gratuities for Beauty Parlor Operators 25 - 0071, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Garages Gas Stations and Parking Lot Attendants. April 9, 1947 25 - 0072 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Findings on Earnings and Tips Received by Employees of Barber Shops Covered Under the New York Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0073, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Report on Field Economic Mobilization Course of the Industrial College of the Armed Forces 25 - 0074, 1951-1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Hearings Conducted for the Purpose of Establishing the Value of Gratuities Received by Drivers in the Taxicab Industry 27 - 0075, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Findings on Earnings and Tips of Taxi Drivers and Chauffeurs 25 - 0076, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Analysis of Testimony Introduced at Hearings on Proposed Schedule I - Value of Gratuities, Beauty Service Industry 25 - 0077, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Hearings Conducted for the Purpose of Establishing the Value of Gratuities Received by Certain Employees in the Hotel Industry 25 - 0078, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Hearings Conducted for the Purpose of Establishing the Value of Gratuities Received by Service Employees in the Restaurant and Hotel - Restaurant Industry 25 - 0079, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Report of Employment Conditions Buffalo Industrial Area Including Niagara Falls and Lockport 25 - 0080, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Public Hearings on Tips in Bowling Alley Industry. April 10, 1947. 25 - 0081 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Bowling Alley Industry. April 18, 194725 - 0082 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Conduct of Hearing Under Chapter 925 of the Laws of 1942 25 - 0083 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Cases Involving Tips - Cited at DPU I Hearing 25 - 0084, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Re: Rules on Tips 25 - 0085, 1939-1947 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Re: Survey on Reasons for Unemployment 25 - 0086, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Inter-Office Memorandum Inventory of Unemployment, June 1949 25 - 0087 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Canning Industry, New York State 25 - 0088, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Industrial Commissioner Releases Inventory of Available Manpower in New York State; District Figures are Included 25 - 0089, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Syracuse Labor Market Study 25 - 0090, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- The Port of New York Maritime Labor Market Report 25 - 0091, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Summary of California Health Insurance Bills (1945) 25 - 0092 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Some Industry-Wide Wage Rate Increases New York City April 1950 - June 1951 /1 25 - 0093, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Excerpt from 1947 Report of New York State Advisory Council on Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0094, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Report on Survey of Recent Governmental Health Insurance Plans 25 - 0095, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- NYSF: Dept. of Labor. Div. of Placement + Unemployment Insurance - Required Reports 25 - 0096, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Office Managers' Overall Statements On the Organization of the New York City Office of the Employment Service April 1949 25 - 0097 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Clues to the Need for Occupational Analysis and Industrial Services 25 - 0098, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Nonfarm Employment in New York State, 1943-47 25 - 0099, 1943-1948 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Industry in New York State: Principal Source Materials 25 - 0100, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Minutes of the Committee on Policies, Plans and Operating Procedures 25 - 0101, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Division of Placement + Unemployment Insurance Bureau of Research and Statistics Memorandums 25 - 0102, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance Office of Executive Director Albany Tools of Policy 25 - 0103, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Tips in Eating and Drinking Places Summary of Tax and Wage Records Bureau 1945 Survey Results and Related Data 25 - 0104 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Sources for History of Labor Legislation in New York 25 - 0105, 1943-1947 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Regulation of Private Employment Agencies ( A Selected Biography) 25 - 0106, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Health Insurance - Legislation New York State 1935 - 1944, 1945 25 - 0107, 1935-1945 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Unemployment Insurance Benefits for Workers in the State of New York, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  2 booklets in folder.
- Speech to Labor Audiences on Changes in the Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0109, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Key Forms of Interest to Employers Under New York State Unemployment Insurance Law as Amended, 1951 25 - 0110 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Letters Related to State Advisory Council on Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0111, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Handbook for Employers 25 - 0112, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- State of New York Department of Labor Elements of Administrative Analysis 235 - 0113, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Letters Relating to Public Relations - State Advisory Council on Placement and Unemployment Insurance Department of Labor 25 - 0114, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Docs. Relating to the Report of the Committee on Policies, Plans and Operating Procedures 25 - 0115, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- State of New York Department of Labor Albany, N.Y. Time Schedule for the Inauguration of Procedure 25 - 0116, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Docs. Relating to State Advisory Council on Placement and Unemployment Insurance Staffing Pattern 25 - 0117, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Docs. Relating to Bureau of Research and Statistics 25 - 0118, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Docs. Relating to Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0119, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Docs. Possibly Relating to Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0120 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Docs. Relating to State of New York Department of Labor Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0121, 1949- 1950 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- -HEW- Regional Office (NYC) Vocational Ed 25 - 0122, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Docs. Relating to New York State Department of Labor Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance- Various Different Subjects 25 - 0123, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Organization of the Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0124, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Employment Security Superintendents 25 - 0125, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Retrenchment in the Division and Consolidation of Claims Bureau and Placement Services 25 - 0126, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Note on Unemployment Compensation Finance in 1938 25 - 0127, 1938-1942 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Stamp Plans 25 - 0128, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Basic Plan of Operation of an Integrated Employment Security Office 25 - 0129, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Comments on Questionnaire of Interstate Conference of Employment Security on Administrative Standards + Summary of Replies Recrived from State Agencies to Questionnaire on Procurement Standards 25 - 0130, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Availability A Statement on Present Practices and the Status of the Law 25 - 0131, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Availability for Work The Status of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law and Present Practice 25 - 0132, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Availability for Work The Status of the New York Unemployment, Insurance Law and Present, Practices 25 - 0133, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Part One: Typical Interpretations in Past Experience Capability for Work Condition of Eligibility 25 - 0134, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Helping the Job Seeker to Help Himself A Plan for the Development by the New York State Employment Service of Informational Material for the Use of Job Seekers 25 - 0135, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Administrative Considerations Regarding Restriction of Unemployment Benefits for Seasonal Employees 25 - 0136, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Employment Security Operations in New York City Report of Committee on Recommendations Resulting from Survey of Employment Security Operations in New York City 25 - 0137, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Guide to Placement and Counseling of Older Workers 25 - 0138, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Hiring Practices and Preferences of Selected Employers Including Summary of their Comments on the New York State Employment Service 25 - 0139, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Interim Report on Merit Rating - Technical Report Volume One, Two + Appendixes 25 - 0140, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Interim Report on Partial Unemployment 25 - 0141, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Interstate Claims in Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0142, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- The Problem of Partial Unemployment Insurance A Planning Report to the Committee on Partial Unemployment 25 - 0143, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Report to Social Security Administration- Bureau of Employment Security on Program of Improving Unemployment Insurance Office Operations and Establishing Proper Time Factors Therefor 25 - 0144, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Seasonal Employment in the Upstate New York Canning Industry A Report on the Application of Section 508 of the Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0145, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- State Experience with Seasonal Provisions in Unemployment Compensation Laws Prepared for Sub-Committee of Committee on Seasonality 25 - 0146, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Layoffs Caused by Indirect Effects of the Steel Strike - New York State Week Ended August 9, 1952 25 - 0147 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Unemployment Insurance Tax Credits in New York State, 1945-1947 25 - 0148 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Information Pertaining to New York Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0149, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Compilation of Material Implementing the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0150, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Instructions to Employers Subject to the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0151, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Partial Unemployment Insurance A Progress Report to the Committee on Partial Unemployment 25 - 0152, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Partial Unemployment Administrative Studies of Unemployment Insurance and of the Inter-Relation of Partial and Total Unemployment Benefits 25 - 0153, 1939-1941 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Insured Employment in New York State 25 - 0154 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Insured Employees, by Selected Industry January 1940 - June 1944 25 - 0155, 1940-1944 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Estimated Labor Force. New York State, 1940-1947 25 - 0156, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Statistical Analysis of Seasonal Industries and Workers - Memorandum No. 2 Preliminary Survey of Employment and Earnings in the Candy Industry 25 - 0157, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Statistical Analysis of Seasonal Industries and Workers - Memorandum No. 4 Second Report on the Canning Industry 25 - 0158, 1937- 1938 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Statistical Analysis of Seasonal Industries and Workers - Memorandum No. 3 Preliminary Survey of Employment and Earnings in Building Construction 25 - 0159, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- First Supplement Requesting Funds to Provide for the Farm Placement Program 25 - 0160, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- A Description of the Function and Organization of the Office of the Director of the New York State Employment Service June 1949 25 - 0161 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- A Description of the Functions and Organization of the Office of the Metropolitan Director of the Employment Service May 1949 25 - 0162 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Survey Report of a Survey of New York City Placement Offices of the New York State Employment Service 25 - 0163, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- I The Reception Process as Carried on in the New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 0164, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- II The Application Process as Carried on in the New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 1065 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- III The Placement Process as Carried on in the New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 0166, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- IV Counseling as Carried on in New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 0167, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- V Selective Placement of Handicapped as Carried on in the New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 0168 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- VI Employer Visiting and Promotion as Carried on in the New York City Offices of the Employment Service 25 - 0169, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- VII Relations between Insurance Offices and Employment Service 25 - 0170, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- VIIA Relations between Employment Service and Insurance Offices 25 - 0171, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- VIII Labor Union Relations 25 - 0172, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Docs. Related to Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0173, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Docs. Related to Meeting on Survey on Employment Service 25 - 0174, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Survey of Local Office Transactions Under the Day-Base Plan 25 - 0175, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Industrial and Geographic Classification of Employers Subject to the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0176, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Geographic Classification Code Showing Counties and Cities of 10,000 Population or Over 25 - 0177, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Docs. Related to Section 508 of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law, Seasonal Provisions and Canning Industry 25 - 0178, 1939- 1942 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Employment of Women in the Buffalo Labor Market 25 - 0179, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- 25 - 0180 Trend of Employment in the Buffalo Area 1929-1943, 1929-1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Recent Recommendations for Improving Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0181, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Docs. Related to Employment Offices 24 - 0182, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Research and Statistics Survey Made by R.A. Hohaus 11/48 25-0183, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Principal Features of the Hughes-Ashbery Bill and Estimated Effects of the Financing Provisions by Industry and Size of Firm 26 - 0001, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Supplement to Report on Potential Liability of the New York Unemployment Insurance Trust Fund 26 - 0002, 1956-1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- The General Account and Subsidiary Contributions Under the Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0003, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Potential Liability of the New York Unemployment Insurance Trust Fund Under Various Economic and Legislative Assumptions 26 - 0004, 1956- 1962 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Effect of Pension Deductions on Unemployment Insurance Benefits July 1963 - June 1964 26 - 0005, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Pensioners and Unemployment Insurance 26 - 0006, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Partial Unemployment Benefits A Sample Study of Records for the Week Ended November 7, 1971 26 - 0007, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- The Periodic Interview: Test of Effect of Varying Frequency 26 - 0008, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- The Benefit Rights Interview Test 26 - 0009, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Study to Determine Costs of Operating a Standard Unemployment Insurance Local Office in N.Y.C. 26 - 0010, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Solvency 1954 26 - 0011 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Benefit Payment Policy and Practices Under the New York Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0012, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Materials Relating to Certain of the Proposals for Changes in the New York Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0013, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Labor Under the New York Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0014, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Key Facts as to 19 48 1956 Unemployment Fund Experience Under the Law of Each State 26 - 0015, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Survey of Clerical Work on Monetary Determinations and Time Lapse, First Pay Orders Six Upstate Local Offices 26 - 0016, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Commuting in the Syracuse Labor Market Area 26 - 0017, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Thirty-Five Years of Unemployment Insurance 26 - 0018, 1935-1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- State Provisions on Dependents' Allowances in Unemployment Insurance State Experience with Dependents' Allowances 26 - 0019, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Availability for Work The Status of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law and Present Practices 26 - 0020, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Statutory Disqualification for Voluntary Leaving "Without Good Cause Attributable to the Employer" 26 - 0021, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Statutory Disqualification for Leaving Locality 26 - 0022, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Causes of Recent Trends in Rate of Disqualification 26 - 0023, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Summary of Disqualification Reports Prepared for Join Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance 26 - 0024, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Active Search for Work as Evidence of Availability in New York State 26 - 0025, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Stuyvesant Center--First Year 26 - 0026, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Employment Security in New York Sate 1935-1960 26 - 0027 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- GF: New York State Department of Labor Office of Executive Director 26 - 0028, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Counseling in the Employment Service for Youth Older Workers Handicapped Disadvantaged Minorities 36 - 0029, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Study of Claimants Formerly Employed by Domestic Employers Covered Under the Provisions of the Unemployment Insurance Law 26 - 0030, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Sources of Information Used by Local Insurance Offices to Ascertain Disqualifying Conditions 26 - 0031, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Effects of Provision Disqualifying Unemployment Insurance Claimants for Misconduct 26 - 0032, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Effects of Provision Disqualifying Unemployment Insurance Claimants for Voluntary Separation from Work 26 - 0033, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Effect of Disqualifying Income on Unemployment Insurance Benefit Rights in State Laws 26 - 0034, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Refusal of Job Offers by Claimants 26 - 0035, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Disqualifications by Local Offices, by Issue New York State, 1942-1952 26 - 0036 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Statutory Disqualifications for Leaving Employment Because of Domestic Obligations 26-0037, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Special Disqualifying Conditions in State Unemployment Insurance Laws 26 - 0038, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Rights of Pensioners to New York Unemployment Insurance Benefits 26 - 0039, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- State Provisions to Relieve Employers of Experience Rating Charges for Benefits Paid to Disqualified Claimants 26 - 0040, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- New York State Unemployment Insurance Tax Rates 1956 26 - 0041 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Manpower Service- A Reference Guide to Job Recruitment, Training and Placement Aids Available through the New York State Employment Service 26 - 0042, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Report on the General Account July 1, 1951 - June 30, 1954 26 - 0043, 1951-1955 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Report on the Unemployment Insurance Fund December 31, 1975 and the General Account January 1, 1975 - December 31, 1975 26 - 0044, 1954-1975 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  Other dates include June 30 and July 1, - June 30
- The General Account Estimated 1954-56 Experience and Possible Changes in Statutory Provisions 26 - 0049, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Estimated Income and Expenditures of the New York Unemployment Insurance Trust Fund, 1960-1967 26 - 0050 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Draft of Statement on Unemployment Insurance Program 26 - 0051, 1935-1959 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Employment Service Goals + White Collar Offices 26 - 0052, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Wage Rates Paid by Small and Large Establishments in New York City 1965-1967 26 - 0053 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Clasp: Report on Research Findings Based on the Experimental Advisory Service Program for Unemployment Insurance Claimants 26 - 0054, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Pilot Demonstration in Group Training in Job Finding 26 - 0055, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- GF: New York State Department of Labor- Personnel Chart - Bureau of Research and Statistics 26 - 0056, 1946-1956 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Study of Claimants Formerly Employed by Domestic Employers Covered Under the Provisions of the Unemployment Insurance Law in Effect Prior to January 1, 1966 26 - 0057 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Second Report by the Research and Statistics Office on Private Household Workers in New York's Unemployment Insurance System 26 - 0058, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Survey of Workers in Household of Unemployment Insurance Claimants 26 - 0059, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- New York State Unemployment Insurance Tax Rates, 1958 26 - 0060 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Unemployment Among Seamen and Longshoremen in New York City 26 - 0061, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Study Made of Labor in Years Ahead, 1960-1970 26 - 0062 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Drafts Used to Prepare Report for Governor's Committee on Financing 26 - 0063, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- County File - Oswego 26 - 0064, 1962-1967 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- New York State Department of Labor Division of Employment Office of Manpower Development 26 - 0065, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Summary of the Guaranteed Wage Plan for Steel Workers 26 - 0066, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- A Survey Housing Our Seasonal Farm Workers 26 - 0067, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Finding Jobs for People Over 45 Report on Pilot Project of New York State Employment Service 26 - 0068, 1955-1957 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- An Experiment to Estimate Seasonal Hired Farm Employment in New York State 1958+1959 Report 26 - 0069 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Age + Employment Jobs After 45. Is There a Problem? 26 - 0070, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Employment in the Sullivan County Resort Industry 26 - 0071, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Presentation on the Utica Skill Survey-Manpower Outlook and Training Needs "Implications and Activation" 26 - 0075, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Tentative Outline Memorandum on Union Phase Labor Market Survey 25 - 0184, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "Proposal to Establish a Dress Industry Placement Office in New York City" 25 - 0185, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Docs. Related to The Older Worker in the Current Labor, Market, Rochester, New York 25 - 0186, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Analysis of Orders for Older Worker Study, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Tables Relating to Employment of Youth/Teens in New York City 25 - 0188, 1930-1936 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Survey of Prevailing Wage Procedures 25 - 0189, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Wage Rates in United States Employment Service Job Openings Selected Occupations Syracuse, N.Y. 25 - 0190, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Preliminary Report 26 - 0072, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Completion and Employment Experience of MDTA Enrollees in New York State 1963-1965 26 - 0073, 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Summary of Manpower Outlock and Training Needs in the Utica-Rome-Herkimer-Little Falls Area 26 - 0074 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Notes on Utica Skill Survey 26 - 0076 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- "Utica Manpower Study" 26 - 0077, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Excerpts from Utica Area Skill Survey Manpower Requirements and Training Needs 1960 to 1965 in 57 Key Occupations 26 - 0078, 1960- 1965 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Special Information on Employment Opportunities for Youth New York Metropolitan Area 26 - 0079, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Memo: To Pensioners 26 - 0080, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Report on Demand Projections by Industry and Occupation for the Nassau-Suffolk Labor Market Area, 1965-1970 26 - 0081 (Box 16, Folder 17)